I mean, I would say the best thing about maturing is I think you should start to feel good more.
You start to feel more at peace.
You start feeling less frantic because you're not fighting the path.
You just save more energy.
You just feel like lighter.
The worst part is letting go of people, giving yourself grace and forgiveness for the ways you were operating when you weren't mature.
Not even just when you weren't mature.
It's not as if you flipped a switch, but, you know, just your process and taking the opportunity when you can to atone for that.
And I will say this, though, not everybody deserves a whole atonement.
I've had people be like, I met you in 2006 at Boston University and you was stank.
And I can tell that you still got stankness.
And then somebody was like, you know, you owe them an apology.
And it's like, well, you're not getting an apology when you come at me like that.
I ain't that mature.